International Association of Machinists Empire Lodge No. 153 (Auburn, NY) Records 5965
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Association of Machinists Empire Lodge No. 153 (Auburn, NY) Records
1891-1935
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Association of Machinists Empire Lodge No. 153
5965
1.11 cubic feet
1.1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5743727
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 02, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2019
Scope and Contents
The volumes of minutebooks received as part of this accession were filmed previously and returned to donor. See collection #5672mf.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5672 mf: International Association of Machinists, No. 153 (Auburn, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5965 MB: International Association of Machinists Empire Lodge No. 153, Auburn, NY, Memorabilia
Machinists, Labor Unions, New York (State), Auburn; International Association of Machinists; International Association of Machinists, Empire Lodge No. 153 (Auburn, N.Y)
5743727
- Financial Documents, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Administrative Documents and Procedures, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- General Correspondence, 1927-1934 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Financial Documents, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Administrative Materials, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Minutes, 1897-1907 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Minutes, 1912-1916 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Minutes, 1906-1911 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Minutes, 1891-1897 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Ledger, 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Ledger, 1920-1933 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Ledger, 1891-1902 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- I.A.M. Charter Auburn, NY - Empire Lodge #153 (Box 3)